Johnny Science Papers 1948-2000 (Bulk 1988-1998) MSS.268
Fales Library and Special Collections
Johnny Science Papers
1948-2000
1988-1998
Fales Library and Special Collections
Johnnh Science
Science, Johnny, 1955-2007
MSS.268
8.72 Linear Feet
Johnny Science (1955-2007) was a musician, make-up artist, and LGBT community leader. The Johnny Science Papers contain materials that directly relate to Science's music and community leadership, ranging from the early 1980s through 2003. In addition, the collection preserves Science's personal creative exploration, writing, and research.
Arrangement
Within each series, materials are arranged alphabetically by document type, project title, or subject, then chronologically if dated.
Series I: Projects include all of Science's works of personal expression, professional work, research, and LGBT group administrative files.
Series II: Correspondence includes communication organized by type or individual in contact.
Series III: Photography preserves contact sheets, photographs, negatives, and slides pertaining to Science's professional and personal collection. These elements document Science's childhood, his work at Max's Kansas City, with Annie Sprinkle, and with The Drag King Club.
Series IV: Objects include handmade items by Science and personal collectables.
Series V: Video recordings includes elements pertaining to Science's Drag King Club work and personal library. These elements have not been preserved and are not currently available to researchers.
Series VI: Sound recordings includes recordings of music by Science and his personal library. These elements have not been preserved and are not currently available to researchers.
Series VII: Data Storage includes magnetic and optical computer data storage elements. Disks have not been preserved and are not currently available to researchers.
Series VIII: Comic Books includes comic books collected by Johnny Science.
Biographical Note
Johnny Science (b. January 13, 1955) was a musician, make-up artist, and LGBT community leader. Born Susan Elaine Greengras, she first began experimenting with theatrical make-up as a child in Englewood, New Jersey. During 1977 - 1980, Susan studied psychology at Fairleigh Dickensen University and began specializing in gender and transsexuality.
She first began to adopt the surname "Science" while leading a band of the same name and art directing at New York nightclub Max's Kansas City in 1980. It was also during this time that Susan began to advocate for lesbian S&M by occasionally performing with leather implements. After passing as a man during these performances, Susan began making serious inquiries about surgical transition and began taking testosterone.
As a man he answered to a few different names: Johnny Armstrong, Daniel Austen, and John Grant. Johnny became a special effects make-up apprentice and began networking with the "Female-to-Male" community in 1984. In 1987, he was a facilitator and guest speaker at the International Foundation for Gender Education Annual Symposium in Massachusetts, provided "male make-over" techniques, led a discussion of "passing" strategies, and began doing make-up for performance artist Diane Torr. In 1989, Johnny founded the F2M Fraternity and produced its newsletter Rites of Passage. Between 1991 - 1992, Johnny founded The Drag King Club, began to coordinate "Drag-King-for-a-Day" workshops, and collaborated with artist Annie Sprinkle to produce her film "Linda/Les & Annie: A Transexual Love Story." Johnny continued to provide make-up services and represent this community in mainstream media by appearing on the Howard Stern Show, the Phil Donohue Show, and the Joan Rivers Show, to name a few. In 1993, Johnny began producing and hosting a weekly television show for the Manhattan Public Access Television Station called "That Show with Johnny Science / The Drag King Club."
Johnny's desire to pass as a gay male led him to evolve from the lesbian S&M community to the male S&M underground. In the late 1990s he was a member of the Gay Male S&M Activists (GMSMA) and president of the Metro NY Chapter of the National Leather Association. He founded The Jovian Gentlemen, a gay male social group that connected younger and elder males. He passed away in 2007.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Scope and Content
The Johnny Science Papers contain materials that directly relate to Science's music and community leadership, ranging from the early 1980s through 2003. In addition, the collection preserves Science's personal creative exploration, writing, and research. The materials include articles, essays, flyers, illustrations, lyrics, notebooks, poetry, posters, and subject files, as well as source and promotional material for LGBT social groups, club administrative files, graphic design drafts, event photography, and original video and audio recordings.
Provenance
The Collection was donated to the Fales Library by Katherine Rachlin and Chrysoula Artemis-Gomez in 2009.
Gay activists -- New York (State) -- New York.; Gays in popular culture.; Performance art -- New York (State) -- New York.; Music-halls (Variety-theaters, cabarets, etc.); LGBT activism.; Transgender people.; Sprinkle, Annie; Torr, Diane; Science, Johnny, 1955-2007
- Series I: Projects, 220132
  - 8 x 10 Visual Entertainment Magazine - Volume 2000 [Magazine], 220391 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 100 Ways to Disappear and Live Free - Eden Press [Pamphlet], 1972; 220401 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - AARP Modern Maturity - Volume 38, Number 1 [Magazine], January - February 1995; 220404 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Amboy Dukes by Irving Shulman [Book], 1948; 223126 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "A New Subscriber" [Short Story with S/M Survey], undated; 220405 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Adam's World - Volume 1, Number 2 [Newsletter], September 1989; 220418 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "Agenda 1/95 - 10/96", 1995 - 1996; 220420 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - [Art: Clippings], various; 220421 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - [Art: Flyers], various; 220422 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "Art Swipe File: Gay XXX", c1996; 220423 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Australian Women's Forum - #53 [Magazine], April 1996; 220424 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "Awaiting the Weight of the Whip" [by Johnny Science], undated; 220426 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bandanna: The Gay East Coast Leather Scene - Volume 3, Issue 1 and 3 [Magazine], 1996; 220434 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bear Essentials: The Newsletter of the Teddy Bear Leather Club of Virginia - Volume 4, Number 4 [Newsletter], July 1996; 220435 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Bear Paws II [Pamphlet], undated; 220437 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "Best Wrapping Paper Christmas '97" [Notebook], 1997; 220439 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Black Leather in Color - Issues 5-7 [Magazines], 1995 - 1997; 220441 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - The Black Leather Jacket by Mick Farren [Book], 1985; 220446 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    General
    The white book marks are places of interest, please do not remove.
  - "Body Language: Gay Male Essays on Sex, Sexuality, and Sexual Politics - A Proposal" by Lawrence Schimel, editor, undated; 220448 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - [Bondage: Clippings], various; 220452 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Boot Licking Slave by George Wilson [Book], undated; 223127 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Cary Grant by Richard Schickel [Book], 1983; 220455 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - The CDG Dungeoneer - Volume 9, Number 3 [Journal], July - August 1996; 220457 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Chainlink - Volume 2, Issues 3-4 [Newsletters], June - July 1996; 220464 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Collars - Volume 1, Issue 6 [Newsletter], April 1996; 220599 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - "Cover Songs" / "Song Sheets" by Suzy Science, c1980; 220600 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - "Creative Writing 101" by Dan Austen, c1996; 220601 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - D + D [Newsletter], June 1996; 220603 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Daddy the Magazine - Numbers 8-9 [Magazines], 1991; 220604 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - [Dan /John Austen Work Flyers], undated; 220602 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - The Decadent Cafe's Bourbon Reader - Volume 2, Number 2 [Zine], 1991; 220605 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - "Diary of a Pansexual Slaveboy" by Danny Boy Austen, 1992, 1995; 220606 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - "Dirty Reader Survey", undated; 220613 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - "Dr. Science Cures Computerphobia" [Flyers], undated; 220615 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - [Drag Kings: Clippings], 1990 - 1999; 220626 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - [Drag Kings: Flyers], c1996 - 1998; 220620 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Dungeon Master - Yearbook 1 [Newsletter], 1979; 220628 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Dungeon Master - Numbers 1, 3, 7-9, 11-12 [Newsletters], 1979 - 1981; 220641 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Dungeon Master - Numbers 14-20 [Newsletters], 1982 - 1983; 220644 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Dungeon Master - Numbers 21-22, 24, 29 [Newsletters], 1983 - 1984, 1989; 220645 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Eat Leather: Eclectic Apparel Toys [Catalog], undated; 220647 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Engle Log 1972 - Dwight Morrow High School [Yearbook], 220648 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Engle Log 1973 - Dwight Morrow High School [Yearbook], 220649 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Ever Leonard: A Service in Celebration of the Life of Leonard John Davis [Book with Project Proposal], February 15, 1997; 220650 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - F2M Fraternity: [Administrative File], c1994 - 1999; 220651 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - F2M Fraternity: "F2M Info-Book #1" [Manuscript], 1990; 220652 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - F2M Fraternity: [Flyers, Membership Forms], April 1991; 220653 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - F2M Fraternity: [Hormones, Phalloplasty Resources], c1991; 220654 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - F2M Fraternity: [Index Cards], undated; 220655 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - F2M Fraternity: Rites of Passage - Volume 1, Number 1 [Newsletter], March 1989; 220656 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - F2M Fraternity: Rites of Passage - Volume 1, Number 2 [Newsletter], December 1989; 220657 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - F2M Fraternity: The Drag-King Club [Administrative File], 1995 - 1999; 220665 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - F2M Fraternity: The Drag-King Club [Administrative Red Notebook], c1992; 220666 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - F2M Fraternity: The Drag-King Club [Contact Lists], c1992 - 1999; 220667 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - F2M Fraternity: The Drag-King Club [Diane Torr], c1995; 220668 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - F2M Fraternity: The Drag-King Club [Drag Ball Photography, Press], 1992; 220673 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - F2M Fraternity: The Drag-King Club [Flyers, Graphics], c1992, 1995; 220669 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - F2M Fraternity: The Drag-King Club [Johnny Science, Make-Up Artist], 1999; 220670 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - F2M Fraternity: The Drag-King Club [MNN Guidelines], 1993, 1995; 220671 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - F2M Fraternity: The Drag-King Club [Shelly Mars], c1997; 220672 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - F2M Fraternity: The Drag-King Club [Workshop Materials], c1992; 220674 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - F2M Fraternity: "That Show with Johnny Science" [Limited Consent, Release Forms], 1999; 220675 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - F2M Fraternity: "That Show with Johnny Science" [TV Graphics], 1998; 220676 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Factor Press: "Celebrating the Bodyspirit" [Catalog], 1992; 220677 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Fig Leaf: The World's Finest Gay Entertainment! - Volume 2, Issue 29 [Catalog], undated; 220678 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - [Film: Clippings], 1990s; 220679 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - [Film: Flyers], 1990s; 220680 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - "FTM 101: Dispelling Myths About the Invisible and the Impossible" by Katherine Rachlin, Ph.D., 1997; 220681 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - FTM Newsletter - Issues 20, 23-24, 1992 - 1993; 220682 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - FTM Newsletter - Issues 26-28, 1994 - 1995; 220683 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Fuzzbox: At War Issue - Volume 2, Number 5 [Zine], Fall 1991; 220684 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Gay Male S/M Activists: [Member Materials], c1996; 220685 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - "Gay XXXmas Carols" by Johnny Science, 1987; 220686 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - [Gender: Clippings], 1990s; 220687 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - "Gender Pretenders: A Drag King Ethnography" by Lauren W. Hasten, February 1999; 220688 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Girth + Mirth of New York: Fat Apple Review [Membership Materials, Newsletters], 1990s; 220689 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Green Egg - Volume 27, Number 104 [Journal], Spring 1994; 220690 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - The Guide: Gay Travel, Entertainment, Politics + Sex [Magazine], June 1996; 220691 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - A Handbook for Dungeon Masters & Mistresses Published by Orgasm, 1990; 220692 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - "Hanky Code" by Johnny Science, 1/8/96; 220693 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - HX for Her - Issue 17 [Magazine], April 30, 1997; 220694 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - HX: Homo Xtra - Volume 5 #43, Volume 3 #12, #385, #424 [Magazines], 1995, 1999; 220695 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - "I am Male. I am a Man." by Johnny Science, undated; 220696 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - [Illustrations by Johnny Science], undated; 220697 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - "Independence Day" by Charles John Austen, July 4, 1985; 220698 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Information for the Female to Male Cross Dresser and Transsexual, 3rd Edition by Lou Sullivan, October 1990; 220699 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - In Uniform - Issue 11 [Magazine], 1998; 220700 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - "The Johnny Science Story", c1999; 220701 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: [Administrative File], 1996 - 1998; 220702 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: "An Ancient Dance" [Flyers], undated; 220703 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: [Binder of Flyers], undated; 220704 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: "April Fool's Play Party" [Flyers], undated; 221637 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: [Black Notebook], c1995; 221638 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: [Blank Calendars], 1996; 221639 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: "Boots Scrap-Book", undated; 220707 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: "Boots Scrap-Book" [Assorted Clippings], various; 220708 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: [Cardstock Print], undated; 221640 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: "Crew Cuts Party" [Flyers], undated; 220709 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: [Flyers Source Materials], various; 220710 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: [Font Samples, Typeface], undated; 221641 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: [Halloween File], undated; 221642 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: [Holiday Clippings], c1996; 220711 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: "Holiday Social" [Flyer Mock-Ups], undated; 220712 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: [Jupiter Flyers], undated; 220713 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: "Kick Back & Relax" [Flyers Materials], undated; 220714 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: "Leather Night" [Flyers], undated; 220715 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: "Levi & Leather Party" [Flyers], 1997; 220716 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: "Membership Forms / Statement of Purpose", undated; 220717 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: "Monday Night Socials" [Flyers], c1995; 220718 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: [Play Party Leather Duo Flyers], 1990s; 220720 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: [Play Party Three-Way Flyers], 1990s; 220721 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: [Play Party Tuxuedo Flyers], 1990s; 220722 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: [Play Party - Various], 1990s; 220719 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: "Safesex Play Party" [Flyers], 1998; 220723 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: "Sex & the Single Sexagenarian" [Flyers], 1990s; 220724 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: "Tuesday Night Socials" [Flyers], 1990s; 220725 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: [St. Peter Flyers, Images], undated; 221645 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - [Juvenilia], undated; 220726 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - "The Kinky Night Before Christmas" by Tony Papajohn, 1995; 220727 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - The Lavendar Line - Volume 2, Number 2 [Newsletter], Spring 1996; 220728 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - [Leather: Clippings], various; 220729 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - [LGBT: Clippings], various; 220733 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - [LGBT: Clippings - Body Image/Weight], various; 220734 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - [LGBT: Clippings - Seniors], c1996; 220735 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - [LGBT: Flyers], various; 220736 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - [LGBT: Flyers - Seniors], c1996; 220737 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Liebography - Issue #2 [Zine], 1999; 220740 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - "Linda/Les & Annie" [Video Promotional Material], c1990; 220741 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - [Literature: Clippings], 1990s; 220738 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Locker Room Tales / ManTalk: [Annotated Clippings], undated; 220742 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - "Master-Slave Contract" by J. Dan Austen, undated; 220756 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Metamorphosis: The Newsletter Exclusively for F-M Men - Volume 1, Numbers 1-6, February - December 1982; 220757 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Metropolitan Slave - Volume 2, Issue 9 and Volume 3, issue 14 [Magazines], Fall 1994, Winter 1995; 220758 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - MNNews - July/Oct 1994, Sept/Dec 1996, Winter 1997, Fall 1998 [Program Newsletters], 1994, 1996 - 1998; 220759 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Modern Maturity - Volume 38, Number 3 [Magazine], May - June 1995; 220760 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - "Mr. Northeast Drummer" [Event Program], 1997; 220762 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Mr. S. Leather Company & Fetters USA Catalog, c1991; 220761 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - [Music: Flyers], various; 220763 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Myths & Legends of Wales by Tony Roberts [Book], 1979; 223141 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - National Leather Association: [Administrative File], c1994 - 1996; 220764 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - National Leather Association: "April Showes" [Flyers], 1996; 220765 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - National Leather Association: "Are You Curious?" [Flyers], undated; 220766 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - National Leather Association: "Art for The Inquistor", c1995; 220767 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - National Leather Association "The Art of Spanking" [Flyers], 1996; 220768 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - National Leather Association: "Boots & Uniform" [Clippings, Flyers], 1996; 220769 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - National Leather Association: "Bulging Boobs & Balls" [Flyers], 1996; 220772 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - National Leather Association: Calendar of Events, 1993, 1995, 1996; 220774 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - National Leather Association: "Fundamentals of Flagellation" [Flyers], 1996; 220775 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - National Leather Association: "Hands on Flogging" [Flyers], 1996; 220776 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - National Leather Association: "Hidden Desires" [Flyers], 1993; 220778 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - National Leather Association: The Inquisitor - Volume 3, Numbers 1 & 4, Volume 5, Issue 1 [Newsletters], 1993, 1995; 220779 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - National Leather Association: "Intergenerational Play Party" [Flyers], 1996; 220782 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - National Leather Association: "Kinky Story-Time" [Flyers], undated; 220785 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - National Leather Association: "Kinky Video Party" [Flyers], 1996; 220786 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - National Leather Association: "Lash Mates" [Flyers], April 1994; 220787 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - National Leather Association: "Leather Pride" [Flyers], 1996; 221141 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - National Leather Association: "The Leathermen's Menu", Thanksgiving 1996; 221142 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - National Leather Association: The Link - Issue 8, #1 [Newsletter], January/February 1994; 221143 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - National Leather Association: [Logo Graphics], undated; 221144 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - National Leather Association: "The Lore of the Lash" [Flyers], 1996; 221145 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - National Leather Association: Membership Application, undated; 221146 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - National Leather Association: MNY Chapter Collection of Flyers, 1995 - 1996; 221147 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - National Leather Association: "The Mummy's Wrap" [Pamphlet Mock-Ups], undated; 221148 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - National Leather Association: "A Night in Hellfire" [Flyers], 1995; 221149 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - National Leather Association: "Pony Boys/Girls" [Flyers], undated; 221150 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - National Leather Association: The Scarlet Leather - Volume 3, Issues 2-3 [Newsletters], March - June 1996; 221151 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - National Leather Association: Statement of Purpose, c1992; 221152 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - National Leather Association: "Pansexual Play Party" [Flyers], undated; 221153 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - National Leather Association: "Strap & Paddle Party" [Flyers], undated; 221154 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - National Leather Association: "Shrimper's Delight" [Flyers], 1996; 221155 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - National Leather Association: "S/M Survey", May 11, 1992; 221156 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - National Leather Association: "What's a Bottom?" [Flyers], undated; 221157 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - National Leather Association: "Whips" [Scrap Book Images], c1995; 221158 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - National Leather Association: "The Year In Review" [Flyers/Fragments], 1996; 221159 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - New York Native - Issue 687, June 17, 1996; 221160 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - NewsLink: The Newsletter of Gay Male S/M Activists - Numbers 24, 34-36, 38, 1992 - 1993, 1995 - 1997; 221161 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - NEXT Magazine - Volume 4, Issue 39, April 11, 1997; 221162 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - [Nightlife: Flyers], 1990s; 220739 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Noose Letter: Hangman's Noose Club - Issue 5 [Newsletter], Fall 1995; 221163 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - The Official 1995 Drag King Calendar, 221164 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - On the Wilde Side - Volume 4, Number 1 [Magazine], November 1995; 221165 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - "Original Songs" by Johnny Science, undated; 221697 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Outlaw Biker Tattoo Revue #5 - Volume 2, Number 3 [Magazine], 1989; 221166 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - The Paper Trip II, Published by Eden Press, 1987; 221167 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - The Petal & The Thorn: The Black Rose Newsletter, May/June 1996; 221168 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - The Penis Press - [Annotated Magazine with Illustrations by Johnny Science], 1979; 221169 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - [Periodicals, Literature: Flyers], c1997; 221170 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - [Phalloplasty / Transgender Health: Clippings], various; 221171 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Playbill Magazines, 1995 - 1998; 221172 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - [Pocket Notebook], undated; 221173 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - [Pocket / Day-Timer Planner], July 1989; 221174 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - [Poetry by Johnny Science], various; 221175 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - [Politics: Clippings], various; 221698 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Porn Free - Issue 7 [Zine], 1996; 221176 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Powerplay #7 [Magazine], August 1995; 221177 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - The Prime Timer - Volume 5, Number 7 [Newsletter], July 1992; 221178 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - [Professional Profile / Resume Drafts], c2000; 221179 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - [Record Book], c1971; 221180 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - [Red Notebook - Poetry], 1978; 221181 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Red Tails: The Newsletter for the Spanking Enthusiast - Volume 20, August 1995; 221182 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - The Renegade - Volume 5.2 [Newsletter], March / April 1996; 221183 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - "Risqué Guys Glee Club" [Music, Flyers], c1999; 221184 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - "Rites of Passage" by Johnny Science, 1991; 221189 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - The Sage [Newsletters], August - September 1996; 221199 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - The Sandmutopia Guardian & Dungeon Journal - Issues 3, 4, 1988 - 1989; 221205 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Sandmutopia Supply Company - Catalog 3, Supplement 1, 1983; 221206 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Science: [Cardboard Art], undated; 221207 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Science: [Collages / Flyers Mock-Ups], undated; 221208 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Science: [Songs, Song Sheets, Servicemark Contracts], 1979 - 1983; 221211 (Box 4, Folder 64)